[Music]
What's going on everyone? Welcome back
to another tutorial. My name is Miran
Kuracosian. Today we're going to focus
on the airw walk. Now, if you've been
watching my tutorials, you know I've
already done the moonwalk in place and
I've also done the slide step that are
very similar and you could catch those
at the end of this video if you want to
go ahead and look at them. But today,
we're focusing on the airw walk. So, the
way we're going to start this turn
around profile. We're going to start
with the right leg. The right leg goes
out. Now, as you bring it slowly, you
want to go on your toes on the left leg.
Okay? So, you hear one. Bring it back.
Left leg goes toe. Whoop. Here. And then
you switch. Left leg and bring it back.
Right leg, bring it back. Left leg,
bring it back. Yeah. Let's try that a
couple of times. Here we go. But we're
going to start with the right leg. Six.
Seven. Eight. We're going one. So step
and two. Switch legs. Three and four.
Five. And six. Seven and eight. Good.
Let's do it again. Five 6 7 8. We're
going 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8. Good. Let's try
that again. 5 6 7 8 go. One
2 3
4. Good. So, it's very important that
you get the timing because it's all
about timing. So, when the leg comes out
and you've already you're straight all
the way through. Now, when you bring it
back, you got to slowly come up on your
toes on the opposite leg. Yeah. To
create that illusion that you're
walking. So, you're here and switch. So,
you want to time that perfectly here.
Switch. One more time. Here. Switch.
Here. Switch. Good. Let's do that again.
Five, six, seven, eight. Go. One, 2, 3,
4, 5, 6, 7, 8. Good. One last time.
Five, six, seven, eight. Go. One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Good. So, keep working on that step.
Now, the way to make it look even
cooler, if you know how to isolate your
neck and you know how to move your body,
you add a little bit of that and the
move totally changes. It becomes even
cooler. So, you're here, you work with
the upper body. Boom, step, boom, step,
hit, step, hit. So, I would say once you
feel comfortable with the legs, add a
little bit more to it. Okay. So, one
last time. Again, I'll do it slow. Leg
comes out. Yeah, just make a full step.
Bring it back. One more time here. Bring
it back. Three. Bring it back. Four.
Bring it back. All right, guys. So, that
was the tutorial for the air walk. If
you want to work on similar steps, you
will see a link after this video to the
moonwalk in place and the slide step. I
would suggest you learn all three moves
cuz they're very similar. Um, other than
that, leave all your comments in the
comment box. Please let me know what you
want to work on. I'm doing this every
week, so I want to get those comments. I
want to help you out. I'll see you guys
next week with a new video.
[Music]